// Answer text must be under 25 characters otherwise they'll be truncated
// Answer value but be the lowecase LETTER of the correct answer (a, b, c, or d)

module.exports = {
  gameType: 'text',
  questions: [
    {
      question: 'Which of the following is a hardwood?', 
      a: 'Pine',
      b: 'Fir',
      c: 'Balsa',
      d: 'Spruce',
      answer: 'c'
     },
     {
      question: 'Which of the following is a softwood?', 
      a: 'Birch',
      b: 'Cedar',
      c: 'Cherry',
      d: 'Oak',
      answer: 'b'
     },
     {
      question: 'The hardness of wood is ranked by what scale?', 
      a: 'Janka',
      b: 'Avery',
      c: 'Stumpage',
      d: 'Kesha',
      answer: 'a'
     },
     {
      question: 'What is Woody\'s last name from Toy Story?', 
      a: 'Wayne',
       b: 'Cowboy',
       c: 'Pride',
       d: 'Harrelson',
      answer: 'c'
     },
     {
      question: 'Which hit show about wood loggers is currently airing on History Channel?', 
      a: 'Ax Men',
       b: 'Swamp Loggers',
       c: 'Tree Fellers',
       d: 'Chainsaw Jugglers',
      answer: 'a'
     },
     {
      question: 'What country does the US have a softwood lumber dispute with?', 
      a: 'Great Britain',
       b: 'Mexico',
       c: 'Canada',
       d: 'Australia',
      answer: 'c'
     },
     {
      question: 'In the musical "Into the Woods," who played the witch in the original broadway cast?', 
      a: 'Glenn Close',
      b: 'Liza Minnelli',
      c: 'Barbra Streisand',
      d: 'Bernadette Peters',
      answer: 'd'
     },
     {
      question: 'Wood ear mushrooms are also known as what?', 
      a: 'Pig\'s Ear',
      b: 'Black Fungus',
      c: 'Chanterelle',
      d: 'Matsutake',
      answer: 'b'
     },
     {
      question: 'Which WWE wrestler was known for using a 2x4 piece of wood as a prop to intimidate his opponents?', 
      a: 'Buzz Sawyer',
      b: 'Drill Presser',
      c: 'Hacksaw',
      d: 'Biscuit Joiner',
      answer: 'c'
     },
     {
      question: 'How much wood could a woodchuck chuck (if it was equivalent to digging a burrow)?', 
      a: '20 lbs',
      b: '75 lbs',
      c: '115 lbs',
      d: '700 lbs',
      answer: 'd'
    }
  ]
};